wpmlm.com 2015-04-16

# Privacy Policy | WP-MLM

  * Privacy Policy

The World's Only Forced Matrix Recruiting System For Reps!

## Privacy Policy

Strongbox Solutions, LLC (“wpmlm.com”, “we”, “us”, or “provider”) will not trade, sell, make available or disclose to any third party any form of personal information without your consent. We value our customers (“you”, “user”, or “end-user”) both current and potential, and want to ensure their privacy when using our services. The following Privacy Policy is enacted to explain how we collect and use information from our customers who use services from wpmlm.com and those who may have visited our website or communicated with wpmlm.com.

Collection, Use, and Communication of Information (by wpmlm.com and/or Third Parties)

In order to use services provided by wpmlm.com, personally identifiable information, including but not limited to name, physical address, email address, telephone number, credit card information and other personal information, must be collected. The customer is responsible for accurate and updated information on file with wpmlm.com. wpmlm.com will not disclose any of the user’s personally identifiable information unless required by law or in order to investigate unlawful activity and/or fraud.

wpmlm.com may also collect non-personally identifiable information from customers and visitors regarding usage of our services or our web site and the viewing of our emails. This may include web site pages viewed, time spent using certain services, IP address, emails opened or blocked, cookies and other information which does not specifically identify any one individual. This information may be shared with third parties by wpmlm.com. The end-user may choose to disable or restrict the placement of cookies, but may result in interference of the website’s functionality.

Cookies are used on many websites in order to gather information and enhance the use of our site to the end-user’s preferences. We are not able to gather personally identifiable information through the placement of cookies unless the user is registered for our site and has purposely given wpmlm.com personal information. wpmlm.com may also use tracking pixels in order to track the number of visitors to our site and the amount of time spent on each webpage.

wpmlm.com will use non-personal information to market services to customers and visitors that wpmlm.com believes may be of interest to them. This may be done through emails, newsletters, banner ads, etc. We may use third parties in order to do this and will not share your credit card information with any third parties unless they are involved in processing payments for services that you have purchased from wpmlm.com.

wpmlm.com will not read or disclose to any third parties private e-mail or other communications that are transmitted using wpmlm.com services except as required to ensure proper operation of services or as otherwise authorized by law. The end-user is liable for any personal information that he or she voluntarily makes available through publicly accessible Internet mediums, such as forums, blogs, and instant messages, and assumes all risks for partaking in such activities that cannot be controlled by wpmlm.com.

Security

wpmlm.com is committed to providing secure and reliable service and has security measures in place to ensure no personally identifiable information may be obtained from outside parties. However, the end-user must always practice caution whenever using the public Internet and acknowledges the risks involved when sharing personal information online.

wpmlm.com has zero tolerance for spam. Please see the Terms of Service to read about wpmlm.com’s infractions against those who are found guilty of using our services for spam.

Deletion of Accounts

wpmlm.com will delete all private information on cancelled accounts unless obligated by law to retain the information. wpmlm.com will never sell or give your private information to any other companies after you have cancelled an account.

## Policy Changes

wpmlm.com reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. Customers will be notified only if the change affects the usage of personal information that was obtained before the policy change. You accept such changes by continuing use of our services.

Click here to view our Terms of Service

## Contact

Email: support@wpmlm.com

**Mail:**

WP-MLM  
2719 SE Sunflower Ct  
Hillsboro, OR 97123
